comparometer.in 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy

###  How we collect information?

Comparometer always respects your Privacy and we use the best IT security measures to keep all your personal information safe and protected. We At comparometer.IN want you to know how, what and when we collect and use information that you decide to share with us while using comparometer. in such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and email address ("personal information"). If we make any changes to our privacy policy, we will post a revised Privacy Policy on this page. If you have any questions, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) By using/browsing/registering with comparometer.in and by submitting your personal data on the Website, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

### What Information is collected?

The information personal or non personal is collected when you access, visit, browse our website or shop through it.

### Why we collect information?

We collect information about you to offer an enhanced shopping experience with us. This is categorized into 2 types –

1) Personal – This information is absolutely provided by your own choice when you create an account with us or may wish to subscribe certain services from us. This may include your name, email ID, profile picture, date of birth, mobile number etc. You may provide this information directly to us or you may chose to register using your Facebook or twitter account in which case you would authorize us to access certain Facebook profile information including your first name, last name and email address. It is not mandatory to provide this information but if you don't provide it, you won't be able to use some of the services we offer.

2) Non – Personal – This information is gathered automatically when you visit, browse or shop from our website. This information includes:

\- Your computer's IP address

\- Your preferences and settings (time zone, language, etc.)

\- Your mobile device's geographic location (specific geographic location if you've enabled collection of that information, or general geographic location automatically)

\- The product searches you submit, results you selected, and pages and products you viewed

-The ads you clicked on

\- How long you viewed our websites and which services and features you used

### How the information is used?

The information is collected to make your shopping experience even better with us. We work on various possibilities and factors to empower you with the seamless, exciting and transparent shopping experience. Shopping should be fun, not a chore! That’s why the website is full of useful tools, to make your shopping all the more interesting.

### Cookies

When you visit our websites, we do use "cookies" on your computer to recognize you. We Collect your non-personal information which is used to make your shopping experience even better with us. The usage of these cookies can be prevented by adjusting the privacy settings in your browser. However, it is not recommended as you may not be able to access the Website and its features properly.

Comparometer.in contains links to the websites of third parties. We should not be held responsible for the actions of these third parties, including their privacy practices and any content posted on their websites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use personal information. Comparometer strictly adheres to industry recognized standards to secure & safeguard any personal information in our possession against any unauthorized access and tampering.

### Copyright

We understand the security of your personal information. We have various security norms to safeguard your privacy. Comparometer will not sell, trade, discloses your personal information to any third party unless:

1) it is absolutely necessary in order to provide you with a specific Service you would have requested 2) it is required of Comparometer in order to comply with a legal process in any applicable jurisdiction (e.g., court order, search warrant, law enforcement 3) it is required by our partner websites, affiliates, advertisers etc. 4) they are the service providers or vendors whom we assign the contract for email messaging, sms services, conduct surveys or provide us analytics to how our website is being used etc.

### Children`s privacy

All content of this website, including, but not limited to, artwork, graphics, images, illustrations, photographs, text, video, audio clips, logos, and designs are the intellectual property of the Company, it affiliates, or third parties who have licensed the materials to us. All content is protected by copyright, trademark, and other intellectual property laws of India. This website in its entirety including, without limitation, the design, layout, selection, coordination, and enhancement of the content, is protected by all copyright and applicable laws.

### Please feel free to contact us at: 

We may not be able to serve the children below 18 years old. We may not collect any information for a child below 18 years knowingly. We respect & feel our social responsibility towards children below 18 years; therefore the website may not allow kids below 18 to create an account with us. If you think we have fallen short at any time, we would love to hear from you - you can be sure we will always listen and work to put it right.
